Bibek KC



info@kc-bibek.com.np



linkedin.com/in/bibek44



010-4881-2332



https://kc-bibek.com.np

Summary

Hello! I'm Bibek K C from Nepal. I am passionate about learning new things and interested in technology-oriented activities that use AI tools and new technologies to solve any existing problems. I have experience working with various technical stacks and I am always open to learning and exploring new ones. In my free time, I enjoy playing sports and listening to purpose-driven startup stories and political activities. I am a senior undergraduate in KAIST and double majoring in Electrical Engineering and Computer Science. If you want to know more about me, you can chat with my assistant B-Bot at https://bibekbot.streamlit.app.

Experience



Research Intern

Robust Intelligence & Robotics Lab, KAIST

Jul 2022 - Dec 2022 (6 months)

Worked on developing a combined framework for realtime 6D Pose Estimation and Scene Graph Generation (SGG) in Robotic Manipulation Task. I used Cosypose framework for 6D pose and Neural Motif framework for SGG and performed experiments on custom cup datasets.

- For a single moving camera setup, estimated 6D pose and generated dynamic scene graphs.
- For 2 fixed camera setup, developed a probabilistic multi-view object-pose estimation framework that (i) associates multiple estimation results with scene graphs, (ii) combines pose distributions from singleview based estimators, and (iii) constructs a unified scene graph by predicting a unified pose distribution per object using MC dropout.

Backend Developer Intern

Bisonai

Jan 2022 - Feb 2022 (2 months)

- Built data pipelines (DAGs) in Airflow to collect DeFi data from various sources like Uniswap, Coingecko and stored them in MongoDB Atlas.
- Implemented backend API server using FastAPI and Strawberry (Python GraphQL Library) to provide DeFi data from MongoDB for users interested in knowing DeFi data from multiple Decentralized Exchanges



Data Viz Project Intern

Interactive Computing Lab, KAIST

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021 (2 months)

 Made a course material for Data Visualization class i.e. a simple tutorial for visualizing plots with Vegalite and D3.js in Observable notebook for beginners to learn Data Viz techniques using Javascript track.

Teacher Assistant

The British College, Kathmandu Jul 2017 - May 2018 (11 months)

Conduct tutorial lectures and helping sessions- help/guide students if they have problem understanding any topics of the course (Chemistry, Physics, Mathematics and Biology)

Education



Fusemachines

Microdegree™, Artificial Intelligence 2023 - 2024

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology

Bachelors, Electrical Engineering and Computer Science Aug 2019 - Aug 2023

Tsinghua University

Global Summer School 2021, Al and Sustainable Development Goals Jun 2021 - Jul 2021

British Model College

High School Diploma, Chemistry, Biology, Physics, Mathematics 2015 - 2017

Skills

Python • Git • Robot Operating System (ROS) • C • Linux Server • FastAPI • Docker • Computer Vision • PyTorch • Vegalite, D3.js

Honors & Awards



Social Innovation Award - Tsinghua University

2021

Won the Social Innovation Award in SDG Hack 11, TSINGHUA GLOBAL SUMMER SCHOOL 2021 with topic 'Al to Solve Education Accessibility Problems in Rural Areas'

Country Topper in AS Level Chemistry - University of Cambridge

Nov 2016

Best student of the batch 2015/2017 - The British College, Kathmandu

2017

Awarded on the basis of academic performance and the contributions to the college.

2nd Position in Inter-School Olympiad - Budhanilkantha School

2016